You see, my initial approach to Kripke
had the same deficiencies...
(Sheldon:)...as those that plagued Stu the Cockatoo
when he was new at the zoo.
(Raj:)Stu the Cockatoo?
(Leonard:)Yes. He's new at the zoo.
(Sheldon:)It's a terrific book. I've distilled its essence
into a simple flow chart...
...that will guide me through the process.
(Howard:)Have you thought about putting him
in a crate...
(Howard:)...while you're out of the apartment?
(Sheldon(on phone):)Hello, Kripke.
Yeah, Sheldon Cooper here.
(Sheldon(on phone):)It occurred to me you hadn't returned
any of my calls...
...because I hadn't offered any suggestions
for pursuing our friendship.
Yeah, perhaps the two of us
might share a meal together.
Yeah, I see.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Well, then perhaps you'd have time
for a hot beverage?
(Sheldon(on phone):)Popular choices include tea,
coffee, cocoa.
(Sheldon(on phone):)I see. No, no, no, wait.
Don't hang up yet.
But what about a recreational activity?
(Sheldon(on phone):)I bet we share some common interests.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Tell me an interest of yours.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Really? On actual horses?